<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existing mod. Leave blank for first publish.-->
	<ModId Value="144908" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="City Watchdog" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
	<ShortDescription Value="Show/Hide notification icons, add/remove Money, set Milestones, Mini HUD, Better Tooltips." />
	<!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<!--LongDescription Value="This is a long description" /-->
	<LongDescription>

#### Display toggles
- [i] button - Instant hide/show **ALL** vanilla mouse-over tooltips.
- 1-click - show/hide 1-way road arrows.
- 1-click - hide/show road name or district.

#### Features
- Notifications: **Instant on/off** toggle for all city alert icons (ones over buildings).
- Reduce visual stress while building (does not fix city problems for you).
- Open full panel from the top-left button or hotkey.
- Start city with any Milestone. Trains now! Yes you can! Set Initial money if you want less for a challenge or more.
- Mini HUD view

#### Money tools
- Quick handy info: hover over bottom menu money/population tooltips for instant info chart (faster than opening Info view).
- Manual: add/subtract money on the fly with hotkeys ([ or ]).
- Optional automatic money refiller. Manual is still recommended.
- Convert saves from Unlimited Money type to normal Limited Money.

Hotkeys
- Shift+N = open/close panel (same as clicking on Top Left icon).
- N    = toggle all notification icons on/off (same as clicking on Toggle All * star button)
- [    = Add Money
- ]    = Subtract Money
- Hold the money hotkey to repeat instead of clicking many times.

### Important Notes
- Check **Show Instructions** for more details or hover over each Options menu row > see details in the 3rd panel on the right.
- City Watchdog hides/shows alert icons and does not fix the underlying problem; get a break until you are ready to fix it.
- Unlimited Money save: make a backup before converting the save. Mod cannot undo that conversion.
- CWD's Tooltip View is a ground-up code write of similar money info to Show Text Trends (DanielVNZ retired).
This viewer uses new methods to do customizable money layouts, settings options, and adds translations.
- Install Achievement Fixer mod if you want Achievements while using mods, it was removed from this mod.

I hope you enjoy the new features, better performance, and safety checks!

### Support and feedback
- Feedback is welcome through GitHub or Discord links on the right.
- If you like effort put into free mods, please give a Like :)
- 15 languages: Hello, Hallo, Hola, Bonjour, Ciao, こんにちは, 안녕하세요, Cześć, Olá, Olá, สวัสดี, Merhaba, Xin chào, 你好, 你好
- If anyone can make better thumbnail or screenshots, please let me know.
- Mod is save safe and safe to remove. Does not use Harmony patch, safer/more compatible. Good for performance: lightweight for daily use.

### Thanks to all supporters and testers
- River Mochi - author/maintainer
- yenyang - locale tech feedback
- Money View inspired by earlier mods by DanielNZ Show Text.
- Notices inspired by the orig. City Controller mod by Mbyron26.
- Dorkington - tester/feature suggestion
- Flightech, SonNathan, Brainium - testers
- UnMaestro - testing, German translation editing
- Thumbnail photograph by Maryia Shedava at Mont Saint-Michel in Normandy, France:
https://unsplash.com/photos/a-dog-poses-in-front-of-a-distant-castle-bEpjaU_CTcM


tags: Visual, UI UX tool tips,UI organize icons, Mini HUD view

</LongDescription>
	<!--Thumbnail-->
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail-dog-city03.jpg" />
	<!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
    <Screenshot Value="Properties/image10-Notifications1.jpg" />
    <Screenshot Value="Properties/image15-Money.jpg" />
    <Screenshot Value="Properties/image20-MinimalPanel.jpg" />
    <Screenshot Value="Properties/image30-HotKeys-ToolTipViewer.jpg" />
    <Screenshot Value="Properties/image40-MiniHUD-Options.jpg" />
    <Screenshot Value="Properties/image50-Milestone-Money.jpg" />
	<!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
	<Tag Value="Code Mod" />
	<!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
	<ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/city-watchdog.1924169/" />
	<!--Version of the mod-->
	<ModVersion Value="1.1.1" />
	<!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
	<GameVersion Value="1.6.*" />
	<!--Dependency for the mod, can be set multiple times-->
	<Dependency Id="" DisplayName="" />
	<!--Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
<ChangeLog>
* Fix - css hover over white.
* Added Mini HUD with icons/totals for top problems in city, see options menu.
* Added Favorites settings for mini hud, draggable, vertical or horizontal, glass panel.
* Added district names
* Other recent major changes:
* Added [i] button toggles on/off ALL game hover over tool-tips.
</ChangeLog>
	<!--External link. supported types are discord, github, youtube, twitch, x, paypal, patreon, buymeacoffee, kofi, crowdin, gitlab-->
    <ExternalLink Type="discord" Url="https://discord.gg/gwXgvtyhjc" />
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/River-Mochi/CS2-CityWatchdog" />
</Publish>
